var myFlashcards = [     {question:"to overcome 103 (too broad because render claim term superflous and not use all terms within claim...)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_13.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>american academy, stumbo and bicon</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble reads on claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_18.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kropa</b></span></a>'},{question:"if clause optional but not optional when 'if' alternative requires another step",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_19.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>johnston, altiris</b></span></a>'},{question:"inherency",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_09.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>levy</b></span></a>'},{question:"meaning of 'about' depends on facts of the case",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-2400-networking-mulitplexing.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ortho-mcneil, pall corp., eiselstein</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble breathes life into claim so preamble can be a limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_22.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wertheim, kropa")</b></span></a>'},{question:"can't read limitations from spec into claims, can't redefine words, disclaimer must be clear and unmistakable.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_23.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Thorner</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim elements listed separately mean distinct components",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering_12.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>becton</b></span></a>'},{question:"disfavored to have single element satisfy two distinct limitations in claim...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering_12.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>CAE</b></span></a>'},{question:"same chemical composition can't have mutually exclusive properties",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_13.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>spada</b></span></a>'},{question:"no patentable combination between device and material it works on",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_14.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>rishoi, young</b></span></a>'},{question:"separate claim elements are construed as separate structures",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_20.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>engel industries</b></span></a>'},{question:"intended use doesn't matter",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_21.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>casey</b></span></a>'},{question:"connected",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_22.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sunrace, ullstrand, and chiron</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim infringed by apparatus encompassing limitations in body not preamble",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/normal-0-false-false-false.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>IMS</b></span></a>'},{question:"Wikipedia unreliable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-2400-networking-mulitplexing.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Three-Dimensional, Bing Shun, Badasa</b></span></a>'},{question:"omit what is well known in the art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_28.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>buchner</b></span></a>'},{question:"product by process",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_30.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>3M, Hazani and Garnero</b></span></a>'},{question:"court can't redefine words",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_09.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thorner</b></span></a>'},{question:"a, an means 'one or more'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/affirmed-in-part-2100-computer.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>baldwin, KCJ, abtox, insituform</b></span></a>'},{question:"includes means comprises, doesn't foreclose additional elements...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sandisk</b></span></a>'},{question:"broadest constuction doesn't give unfettered license to embrace anything",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_30.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>suitco surface</b></span></a>'},{question:"ordinary simple English is clear and unquestionable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_25.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Chef America</b></span></a>'},{question:"non-functional descriptive material no patentable weight",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_25.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Xiao</b></span></a>'},{question:"'consisting of' is closed",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_25.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>AFG</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble necessary when limitations rely on it for antecedent basis",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_07.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>eaton2</b></span></a>'},{question:"Newman case for BRI is an expdient not a rule",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_11.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Skvorecz</b></span></a>'},{question:"only own lexicographer and disavowel for claim term having other than common meaning",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_13.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thorner, aventis</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim construction a matter of law reviewed de novo",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_14.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>cordis</b></span></a>'},{question:"intended use in whereby claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_14.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hoffer and minton</b></span></a>'},{question:"ordinary customary meaning for claim term comes from posita and written description",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_25.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ferguson</b></span></a>'},{question:"from 2007 not old e-pass from 2003 for step order in method claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/mobile-search-reversed-2100-computer.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>e-pass</b></span></a>'},{question:"'coupled to' doesn't require a physical coupling",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-2100-computer.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bradford, johnson worldwide</b></span></a>'},{question:"markush claims - one alternative in prior art is enough",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1600_25.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fresenius, schering</b></span></a>'},{question:"examiner hasn't shown sound basis to shift burden",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1600_25.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>spada, ludtke, king</b></span></a>'},{question:"inherency and prima facie obviousness have equal burden of proof",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1700-chemical_26.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fitzgerald and best</b></span></a>'},{question:"assigning special meaning ok if departure from common usage would be understood by posita",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1700-chemical_26.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>multiform</b></span></a>'},{question:"different terms mean different things",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-1600.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>CAE Screenplates</b></span></a>'},{question:"251 reissue",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>doyle</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI and claim interpretation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-2600_21.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>American Academy of Science, Bicon, Philips</b></span></a>'},{question:"different terms mean different things",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600_31.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>CAE</b></span></a>'},{question:"single structure can't read on multiple claim limitations, claim construction must be reasonable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Intellectual Pro., Kelley</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI -'configured to' defines apparatus by what it does",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-3600.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>aspex</b></span></a>'},{question:"'about' used in numeric range to avoid strict numerical boundary",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600_7.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>cohesive tech</b></span></a>'},{question:"examiner must describe inherent functional limitation.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600_7.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>schreiber, swinehart</b></span></a>'},{question:"surrounding claim language must be considered",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-2400.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ACTV</b></span></a>'},{question:"a for 'one' needs support",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600_20.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>baldwin graphic</b></span></a>'},{question:"must disclaim embodiment in spec to narrow claim scope",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_24.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>eolas</b></span></a>'},{question:"'contain' is open ended",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/de-seversky-strahilevitz-tap.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>TAP</b></span></a>'},{question:"for saying how it is intended to be employed doesn't distinguish prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/angstadt-atlas-powder-falkner-vaeck.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>masham</b></span></a>'},{question:"consistent use of different terms implies different meanings",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/cae.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>CAE Screenplates</b></span></a>'},{question:"claims measure the invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/media-techs-nuijten-tiffin.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>SRI</b></span></a>'},{question:"for non-functional descriptive language",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/lowry.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Lowry</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI needs support in spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/bond-robertson-schriber-schroth-sneed.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bond, sneed, schriber-schroth</b></span></a>'},{question:"diaper case three fasteners don't equal two",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/bond-robertson-schriber-schroth-sneed.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>robertson</b></span></a>'},{question:"can't read particular embodiment into claims if claim language broader...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/mouttet-superguide.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>superguide</b></span></a>'},{question:"'clear linkage or association' of structure to function recited in claim is based on POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/allvoice-ferguson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>allvoice</b></span></a>'},{question:"meaning of 'ordinary' and 'customary'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/allvoice-ferguson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ferguson</b></span></a>'},{question:"recitation of material worked on doesn't differentiate structure",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/epstein-ipxl-rishoi.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>rishoi</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim scope cannot depend on subjective opinion of particular individual, it's a public objective standard",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/datamize-fisher-kao-ricoh.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>datamize</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble gives life, if without it steps are mothing but academic exercise",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/bilski-boehringer-corkill-manziere-mayo.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>pitney, boehringer</b></span></a>'},{question:"intergrated circuit device means chip",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/rambus.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>rambus</b></span></a>'},{question:"'comprising' and 'including' are synonymous",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/biomedino-mars.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mars</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI does apply to patents in reexam but does not apply to expired patents",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/american-academy-bowles-suitco-surface.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>suitco surface, bowles and papst-motoren</b></span></a>'},{question:"reexam of expired patent is not BRI",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/bowles-griver-papst-motoren.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>paptst-motoren and bowles</b></span></a>'},{question:"inventors and attorney's testimony after the fact and of little weight in claim construction.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/amhil-asahiamerica-bell-and-howell.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bell &amp; howell, roton barrier</b></span></a>'},{question:"substantially means largely but not wholly what is specified",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/amhil-asahiamerica-bell-and-howell.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>york, amhil</b></span></a>'},{question:"generally parallel envisions some deviation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/anchor-wall-deering-laryngeal-michalek.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>anchor</b></span></a>'},{question:"for patentee to be lexicographer must put special def in spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/anchor-wall-deering-laryngeal-michalek.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>laryngeal</b></span></a>'},{question:"substantially = 'largely but not wholly, 'largely', 'essentially'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/anchor-wall-deering-laryngeal-michalek.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>york, deering</b></span></a>'},{question:"being configured to language just intended use",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/allen-engg-boehringer-ims-jung-kinetic.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>boehringer</b></span></a>'},{question:"body of claim doesn't depend on preamble",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/allen-engg-boehringer-ims-jung-kinetic.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>storage tech, allen eng., IMS</b></span></a>'},{question:"Unclaimed features cannot impart patentability to claims.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/hiniker-self.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hiniker</b></span></a>'},{question:"for descriptive material to be functional it must transform the claim's method",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/huai-hung-kao-king.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>huia-hung kao, king</b></span></a>'},{question:"inclusion of article or material worked upon by structure does not impart patentablilty",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/otto-thibault-tokai.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thibault, otto</b></span></a>'},{question:"in claim differentiation difference is significant if absence of difference would make claim superfluous",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/comark-free-motion-sjolund-tandon.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>free motion fitness</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 'flatten' needs more to distingush it from some other object",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/playtex.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Playtex v. P.G.</b></span></a>'},{question:"doctrine of claim differentiation - when there are different words in separate claims different meaning presumed, with dependant claim presumed that limitation is not present in independant claim, esp when one party wants lmitation read into independant claim.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/nystrom-phillips-sunrace.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nystrom, phillips and sunrace</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/morris-santarus.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>morris</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim terms include limitations when defined in spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/ccs-mcguire-phillips.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>CCS Fitness</b></span></a>'},{question:"examples in spec can be used to teach POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/ccs-mcguire-phillips.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Phillips</b></span></a>'},{question:"name claim game",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/hiniker-self.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hiniker</b></span></a>'},{question:"can't read limitations from spec into claim.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/hiniker-self.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>self</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim language should not be treated as meaningless",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/bicon-innova-miller-vogel.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bicon</b></span></a>'},{question:"consisting essentially of opens claims to ingredients that don't affect basic characteristics of compositions, but specification must be consulted.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/janakirama-ppg.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>janakirama, PPG</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim preamble limiting when limitation in body relies on it",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/bicon-case-cortright-eaton-richdel.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>zumbriel, bicon</b></span></a>'},{question:"transitional term 'comprising' does not broaden markush group",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/mannesmann-berenter-geneva-symbol.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mannesmann, berenter</b></span></a>'},{question:"printed matter but interrelated to circularity of underlying substrate so new product",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/larson-ntp-jasinski-gulack.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gulack</b></span></a>'},{question:"can't import limitations from spec but can use broader dictionary definition",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/trans-texas-dealertrack.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>trans texas</b></span></a>'},{question:"if body of claim sets out complete invention, preamble not limiting",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/schreiber-altenpohl-fessmann-marosi.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>schumer</b></span></a>'},{question:"conversion from active steps to functional language broadens claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/schreiber-altenpohl-fessmann-marosi.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>schreiber</b></span></a>'},{question:"spec may provide context but not at expense of actual claim language",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/saab-dunbar.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dunbar</b></span></a>'},{question:"spec doesn't have to include subject matter POSITA would commonly understand",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/univ-of-pittsburgh-edwards.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>edwards</b></span></a>'},{question:"spec to impart different meaning must demonstrate intent to deviate from ordinary meaning",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/univ-of-pittsburgh-edwards.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>univ. of pittsburgh</b></span></a>'},{question:"coupled means both direct and indirect coupling",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/medichem-mems-tech-norgren.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mems tech</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim drawn to four-sided generally rectangular clamp means whole clamp is, not just portion",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/medichem-mems-tech-norgren.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>norgren</b></span></a>'},{question:"an express limitation cannot be read out of a claim, BRI not withstanding",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/rouffet-texas-instruments.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>texas instruments</b></span></a>'},{question:"examiner uses BRI",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/biogen-seachange-depuy-spine.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>biogen</b></span></a>'},{question:"preamble does not limit claim unless recites essential structure or steps",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/cordis-allen-engg-catalina-pitney-bowes.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>allen eng, catalina, pitney bowes</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim construction is question of law reviewed de novo",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/cordis-allen-engg-catalina-pitney-bowes.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>cordis</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art apparatus must be able to perform functional limitation in apparatus claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/schreiber-k-2.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>schreiber, k-2</b></span></a>'},{question:"apparatus claim covers what device is not what it does",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/hewlett-packard-aslanian.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hewlett-packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"applicant's remarks submitted with IDS can be basis for limiting claim scope",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/ipxl-katz-interactive-rembrandt-ekchian.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ekchian</b></span></a>'},{question:"general term understood in context inventor presents it",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/glaug.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>glaug</b></span></a>'},{question:"limitation that informs of method's benefits not functional",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/king-ngai-nehls-kao.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kao</b></span></a>'},{question:"for manipulated information must be new and unobvious functional relationship to distinguish prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/king-ngai-nehls-kao.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>king, ngai</b></span></a>'},{question:"optional elements don't narrow claim because can always be omitted",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/johnston.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>johnston</b></span></a>'},{question:"words of claim given ordinary meaning unless inconsistent with spec or prosecution history",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/desper-products.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Desper Products</b></span></a>'},{question:"electrically coupled not limited to directly coupled",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/mems-tech-dairy-queen.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mems tech</b></span></a>'},{question:"even though extrinsic evidence judges free to consult dictionaries and technical treatises",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/vitronics-best-crown-operations-jung.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>vitronics</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI in reexam different than in district court because different burdens of proof",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/kim-greenliant-ergo-katz-interactive.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>NTP, american academy, baxter</b></span></a>'},{question:"connected restricted to neither direct or indirect connection",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/med-instrumentation-mewherter-ullstrand.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ullstrand</b></span></a>'},{question:"a used with open-ended claim containing 'comprising' means 'one or more'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/tate-access-kcj-mccormick-patlex-etter.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>tate access, KCJ</b></span></a>'},{question:"if several common meanings for claim term use patent disclosure",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/renishaw-lister.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>renishaw</b></span></a>'},{question:"claims are construed to give effect to all terms, no claim phrase is superfluous",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/08/eicon-stumbo.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>eicon, stumbo</b></span></a>'},{question:"machine includes every mechanical device that performs some function to produce a certain result",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/08/ferguson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ferguson</b></span></a>'}
     ];
